Now a lot of technique goes into ring throws and it's very different from throwing a ball or a club.
First suggestion for learning how to juggle rings is find a place indoors with a high enough ceiling to practice.
Doing it outside can be great, but rings are usually light enough that the slightest gust of wind will take them off course.
The object of your basic ring throw is to be able to see both sides of the ring as it travels past you.
When it's in one hand you can see the inside.
As it travels through the other side, you see the inside over here.
Meaning you don't want the ring skew outward like this.
The second your ring is skewed inward like this, you've obstructed the path of other rings.
The other thing to remember is that you can cheat a little bit with angling of your wrist.
While you never want the ring to be changed on this plane, you can have it changed on this plane.
This can help guide the path especially for higher throws.
As you see just angling the ring a little bit automatically drove the ring rather out to the side.
Same goes for this side.
That's your basic ring throw.
Once you get that down, the steps are the same as juggling with any prop.
Start with one, add two and then work your way up to three.